## Jean Vides

## Web Developer

I are Jean, Web development lover with experience in React with a strong combination with Redux and for the backend the awesome and incredible Golang, together I can create strong websites with a cute design that can attract more users.

 $\sim$ 

jean@jean.host

+57 3242255480

0

El Copey, Colombia

jeanvides.me

in

linkedin.com/in/jeanvides

y

twitter.com/JeannVides

(7)

github.com/JeanCarlosVR

## **SKILLS**

Frontend Developer

**Backend Developer** 

API Designer

Communication

**Human Resources** 

UI & UX Designer

Event Manager

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Frontend and Backend Developer Jean Services

12/2020 - Present

Contact: contact@jean.host

## NPM Developer and Web Design

**TNAI** 

11/2020 - 02/2021 Puerto Rico

### **ORGANIZATIONS**

Jean Services (05/2020 - Present)

CEO, Frontend Developer, Backend Developer and Project Management

TNAI (11/2020 - 02/2021)

UI & UX Designer, Frontend Developer and NPM Contributor

## **CERTIFICATES**

Node.js Advance (03/2021 - 04/2021)

Interface Design (UI) Essential (03/2021 - 04/2021)

HTML Essential (03/2021 - 04/2020)

HTML & CSS Essential Integration (03/2021 - 04/2021)

HTML Course (02/2021 - 02/2021)

CSS Course (02/2021 - 02/2021)

JavaScript Course (02/2021 - 02/2021)

React + Redux Course (02/2021 - 02/2021)

## **LANGUAGES**

#### Spanish

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

English

Limited Working Proficiency

#### PERSONAL PROJECTS

#### Polls (Discord Service) (01/2020 - Present)

 Polls, is a bot related to the Discord platform, which helps users to conduct polls in their communities. Project repository: https://github.com/JeanCarlosVR/polls-bot

#### Jean Shortener (04/2021 - Present)

 Jean Shortener is an ultra secured and efficient URL shortener. Project repository: https://github.com/JeanShortener

#### **INTERESTS**

Programming

Sports

Movies

#### **EDUCATION**

#### System Technical

Servicio Nacional de Aprendizaje (SENA)

03/2021 - Present

Courses

System Technical

English

El Copey

Colombia